There's one more thing I want to do with my boss's movement.
When my boss is within a certain distance of my character, I want it to stop moving.
So if we go back to our boss blueprint and just right click on this value and break the link and just
right click and go split structure pin and just drag off the X when this value is less than, let's
say, 450 units.
I don't want my boss to move any more.
So if we just drag up here and.
And connect us into here.
If this condition is false, then we'll continue moving.
If it's true, then we'll move towards our player character.
And I just want you to read the print string because I want to show you something.
So if I go compile and play, I am -1326 units away from my boss in the x axis.
If I go over here and this value becomes positive, then my boss will move towards me.
However, when this value is negative, my boss doesn't move towards me.
In order to fix this, we can use the absolute node.
So if I just drag up here, I look for absolute and we want this one absolute flow and just connect
this into here.
And what this absolute float will do is make it so that this value will work with positive and negative
conditions.
So let go, compile and go play.
It doesn't matter if this value is positive or negative, as long as my player character is 450 units
away from my boss character, it will move towards me.
We can now just delete that print string.
I just wanted to show that to showcase the minus values.